# Trương Lê Huy

Front-End Developer

📞 0353528527 👿 lh222k@gmail.com 🔗 truonglehuypf.netlify.app 👂 318 Dũng Sỹ Thanh Khê, Đà Nẵng, Việt Nam

#### **OBJECTIVE**

Hello, my full name is Truong Le Huy. I'm a front-end developer. Over the past two years, I have primarily worked for companies that specialize in enterprise web applications. I primarily focus on writing clean, elegant, and efficient code. With learning experiences and passion for learning new technologies to increase the quality of work. I always want to share my knowledge with the members of the company. Hope I can contribute to the development of the company

#### **EDUCATION**

**FPT Polytechnic** 

2018 - 2021

Application software

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

**Enable Startup Co., Ltd** 

03/2021 - 06/2021

Intern

- Learning and building projects with Reactjs, NodeJS
- Improve teamwork skills

### **Enouvo IT Solutions**

04/2022 - 04/2024

Front-End Developer

I have worked with a variety of different languages, platforms, frameworks, and content management systems such as JavaScript, TypeScript, Next.js/React,....

#### **SKILLS**

ReactJs, NextJs

HTML, CSS, Javasrip,

**TypeScript** 

**Python** 

Tailwind CSS, Ant, Mui

Graphal, RESTfull APIs

#### **PROJECTS**

# **Smartos - smartos.space**

(05/2022 - 04/2023)

Name of customer	Smoart, Enouvo IT Solutions	
Description project	Smartos is a Proptech SaaS product, providing a comprehensive digital transformation solution in Real Estate management through Smartos PMS (Property Management System), Smartos Marketplace application and White Label platform	
Your team size	From 7 to 14 members in the team	
Your position in project	Frontend Developer	
Your responsibility in project	Worked on the front-end development of the website using Typescript, Ant, ReactJS, Graphql     Collaborated closely with the team in regular meetings and interacted with clients	
Technology description	Typescript, Ant, ReactJS, Graphql, Tailwind, Vite	

# nhatrovanminh.com

( 08/2022 - 03/2023 )

Name of customer	nha tro van minh	
Description project	A webapp project providing room rental management services	
Your team size	From 3 to 5 members in the team	
Your position in project	Frontend Developer	
Your responsibility in project	<ul> <li>Implemented website design and enhanced interactivity.</li> <li>Design and code personal websites.</li> <li>Update the new version UI for the website construction</li> </ul>	
Technology description	Typescript, Ant, NextJS, Graphql, Tailwind	

# **Acciona Linkoffice**

(05/2023 - 04/2024)

Name of customer	Acciona	
Description project	Financial management web app project with contracts	
Your team size	From 15 to 22 members in the team	
Your position in project	Frontend Developer	
Your responsibility in project	Conducted testing tasks to ensure website functionality and quality.	
Technology description	Typescript, Ant, ReactJS, Graphql, Tailwind, Vite, Reactgrid	

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

Responsive Web Design - Freecodecamp	2021
JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures - Freecodecamp	2021

#### **HONORS & AWARDS**

**UNIHACK 2022** © topcv.vn

